dubai.com 2016-10-22

# Dubai Holidays, Dubai Hotels - Dubai Travel and City Information

## Privacy Policy

  * 1\. Introduction
    * 1.1. We are committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to the web site in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 (the "Act").
    * 1.2. This privacy policy explains how we may collect personal data and how we use the information we may collect about you.
  * 2\. Information collected and retained by the Administrators 
    * 2.1. We collect personal information about you from personal details provided by yourself in relation to the Services we offer to Users. We do not collect any sensitive personal information such as information on your racial or ethnic origins, political opinions, religious beliefs, trade union affiliations, sexual life, health or criminal history.
  * 3\. Use of information by the Administrators 
    * 3.1. We collect information which is necessary to: 
      * 3.1.1. provide the Services to you;
      * 3.1.2. notify you of your Service order status; and
      * 3.1.3. carry out internal administration and analysis.
    * 3.2. We can also use that information to enhance your visit to our web site by: 
      * 3.2.1. telling you about new products, new services and special offers;
      * 3.2.2. tailoring your experience to your preferred choice of activities; and
      * 3.2.3. informing you of changes in our web site.
    * 3.3. By providing us with your personal information, you consent to us (and where relevant, our subsidiaries, affiliates and trusted partners) using (including collecting, storing and processing) your personal information. We will of course inform you of any changes to Privacy policy and you will have the opportunity to opt out of those changes which affect you. 
  * 4\. Accessing and amending your personal information 
    * 4.1. We will process your personal data for the purposes set out in clause 3 above. If however, you have any queries or requests in relation to Data Protection please use our contact form
  * 5\. Disclosure to Third Parties 
    * 5.1. We may disclose your information to necessary third parties to enable us to provide you with the Services. By requesting us to provide you with the Services you consent to this disclosure.
    * 5.2. We also reserve the right to access and disclose to third parties your information to comply with applicable laws including but not limited to disclosure in accordance with the Act, the Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act 2000 and lawful authority requests, to safeguard the proper operation of our systems and to protect ourselves and our clients.
  * 6\. Protection of personal information 

We use our reasonable efforts, to ensure proper storage and careful disclosure of your personal information in order that nothing improper happens to your private information. These security measures mean that we may occasionally have to ask you for proof of identity before we are able to disclose personal information to you.

  * 7\. External Web Sites 

This privacy policy only applies to this web site. The web site may contain links to external web sites, some of which are displayed within a DUBAI.COM Website Service frame. Please note that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We recommend that you check the privacy policy of any other web sites you may visit through the web site. The inclusion of links to such web sites does not imply any endorsement of the material on such sites nor any association with their owners or operators. If you have any complaints relating to such sites, please contact them directly.

  * 8\. Opt-In 

If you tick an opt-in box the Administrators will provide your information to selected third parties. We or they may contact you by mail, telephone or e-mail to let you know about services and products which may be of interest to you. You have the right to ask for a copy of the information held by us about you in our records in return for the payment of a small fee. You also have the right to correct any inaccuracies in the information.

  * 9\. Use of Cookies 

This website uses cookies. Cookies are small pieces of text that are written to your hard drive to store information about your use of the DUBAI.COM Website Service. You have the right to refuse cookies (please see your web browser's help file for information on doing this), but by doing so you may disrupt the performance of the DUBAI.COM Website Service or make it inoperable to you.

  * 10\. Suppliers 

DUBAI.COM provides information about travel either reserved or purchased on this website to the suppliers whose will fulfill your travel reservation. Although we offers travel products from hotel, airline, car rental and other suppliers that are reputable companies, we have not placed limitations on these suppliers from using or disclosing your information without your permission. Therefore, we encourage you to review the information privacy practices of any travel suppliers whose products you purchase on this website. In addition, these travel suppliers may also contact you as necessary to obtain additional information about your confirmed reservation. DUBAI.COM will occasionally share aggregated information with our service providers. This information does not contain any personally identifiable information and is used to develop featured programs and content that will be of interest to our website visitors.
